<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fixeds on Imperial Blog</title><link>https://imperialmight.com/fixed/</link><description>Recent content in Fixeds on Imperial Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:38:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://imperialmight.com/fixed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About The Game</title><link>https://imperialmight.com/about-the-game/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:38:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://imperialmight.com/about-the-game/</guid><description>Elevator Pitch Imperial Might (IM) is a browser and turn based, multiplayer, persistent world grand strategy game where you compete with other 15 players for power and prestige in a medieval world. Is a never ending game where you interact with fellow Kings using tools related to diplomacy, economy, military and culture.
Your subjects use their free will to move and settle where economic and subsistence opportunities emerge, forming trade routes than then become roads and links to other Kingdoms.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://imperialmight.com/about-me/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 15:38:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://imperialmight.com/about-me/</guid><description>Hello there. I&amp;rsquo;m Gabriel, a 39year old guy from Buenos Aires, Argentina. I&amp;rsquo;m a Business Intelligence Analyst, freelance web developer, IT Engineering undergrad and future husband.
I have always dreamed of making a game and developing it as a business and now I&amp;rsquo;m giving it a real shot. I&amp;rsquo;d like to make it my living and if not, at least I&amp;rsquo;ll learn a lot of new things to beef up my resume.</description></item><item><title>The Imperial Newsletter</title><link>https://imperialmight.com/the-imperial-newsletter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 20:21:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://imperialmight.com/the-imperial-newsletter/</guid><description>Subscribe to the game news. You will not receive new blog post notifications (for that you may check @ImperialMightHQ) but instead meaningful game information and important related events. I&amp;rsquo;ll keep the spam to a minimum. If you subscribe to this I&amp;rsquo;ll know you are serious about the game!
Please enter your email address
powered by TinyLetter</description></item></channel></rss>